Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The American Woman, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Women's Bureau. A Selected Bibliography of Basic Sources. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Economic Responsibility of Women Workers as Shown by a Women's Bureau Study of Women War Workers and their Postwar Employment Plans, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Household Employment, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Women's Bureau. A Digest of Current Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Women as Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The Role of Women's Legislation in Meeting Basic Problems of Working Conditions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Elizabeth S. Magee. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Progress of Women in the United States, 1949-1951, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Some Aspects of the Nightwork Problem with Special Reference to the Restaurant Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Women who Work at Night, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Edward Corsi. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report on Trends in Night Work for Women in New York State Factories, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Employment of Women in an Emergency Period, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Women's Role in the Manpower Program, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: While Mothers Work at Defense Jobs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Children's Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Rosie the Riveter is Coming Back, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Frances Whitelock. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Median Age of Women in the Labor Force, 1900-1950, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: Recommended Standards for Employment of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Womanpower in Mobilization, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Roma K. McNickle. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Women's Stake in Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Standards for Employment of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Women in Higher-Level Positions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: Labor-Force Participation and Employment Opportunities for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Nedra Bartlett. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Why Women Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: A Report on Part Time Employment of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Based on Edna Noble White's Studies. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Women in Labor Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Gladys Dickason. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Working Wives and Mothers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Stella Applebaum. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Working Women and Unemployment Insurance, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: Women's Chances for Advancement in Business and Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Why do Women Work?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: How to Supervise Women Employees, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: A Job for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Health resources Advisory Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Special Problems in the Supervision of Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
    By Elinore Morehouse Herrick. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Employment of Women in Defense Production, Publication (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Some Questions Raised by the Employment of Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Gertrude Inwood. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Employment of Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By L. C. Wagner. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Womanpower, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: Differentials in Pay for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Women and the War Effort, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Robert Goodwin. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Wages of Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Mary Anderson. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Safeguarding the Woman Employee, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Recruiting Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Why we Like Women in our Shop, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By W.G. Guthrie. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Women as Manpower, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Katherine Glover. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Women Work, Women Vote, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: Women in War Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By The Franklin Institute. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: You're Going to Employ Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Should Married Women Work?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Jobs and the Woman, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Ruth Leach. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Women and the Top Jobs, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Ruth M. Leach. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Women in Unions, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Orlie Pell. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Wartime reminders to Women who Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Status of Women in Unions in War Plants, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Women'sBureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Women in Brazil Today, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: Women at Work in Wartime, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: 50 Facts About British Women at War, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 24: Absenteeism and What Every Woman Should and Can do About it, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Whitney Williams. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Working Conference on Women in Business and Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: Women in Postwar Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Frederick Crawford. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: What Job is Mine on the Victory Line?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 28: Analysis of State Equal Pay Laws as of October 15, 1945, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 29: Report on Conference on Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
    By Women's Buresu. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Women in Personnel and Industrial Relations Work in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 31: Journal of Social Case Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 32: Women's Wages in Wartime, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 33: Recommended Standards for Clothing and Personal Protective Equipment for Women Shipyard Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Item 34: Women in Shipbuilding, Publication (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Box 31, Folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Supervising the Woman War Worker, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Women in War Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: War Jobs for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Why Women Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Beulah Amidon. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Planning for Part-time Work, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Health and Welfare of Women in War Factories, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Committee Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Women Who Work in New York, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Safety Fashions for Women in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 9: American Women at War, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Occupations Suitable for Women, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 11: Are You Equal to two German Women?, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Information Notes on Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 13: Women in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    By Department of Economics and Social Institutions. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Women in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: Standards for Maternity Care and Employment of Mothers in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 16: War-time Employment of Women in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Women's War Work in Britain, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 18: Employment of Women in War Production, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 19: Application of State Hour Laws to the Employment of Women on Defense Projects, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Recreation and Housing for Women War Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Safety and Health Problems of Women in Industry, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 22: Use of Women as Makers of War Instruments Studied by Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: State Hour Laws for Women Possible Excemptions in Periods of Emergency in Manufacturing Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 24: Opinion of the Court, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Women Workers in War Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 26: Women in Defense Industries, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
    The Effect of the Increasing Employment of Women on Company Personnel Policies. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Plan Now for Women Workers, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Item 28: White House Announcement, Publication (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Women in Nontraditional Jobs: A Program Model, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Women in Nontraditional Jobs: A Conference Guide, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Young Women and Employment: What we Know and Need to Know About the School-to-Work Translation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Employment and Economic Issues of Low Income Women: Report of a Project, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Women at Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Henry Myers. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Women in Blue-Collar Jobs, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Women in the Economy: Full Freedom of Choice, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Minority Women Workers: A Statistical Overview, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Modern Woman in the Modern Union, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Gloria Johnson. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Working Women for Freedom, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Angela Terrano; Marie Dignan; Mary Holmes. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: State Labor Laws in Transition: From Protetion to Equal Status for Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Employment Needs of Women Offenders: A Program Design, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Career Counseling for Women in the Federal Government, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Federal Women's Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Working with Women: A Handbook for Men, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Staff Recommendations. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Minority Women Workers: A Statistical Overview, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
    By Wmployment Standards Administration. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Mature Women Workers: A Profile, Publication (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Working Women and their Organizations, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
    By Joyce Maupin. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Ten Women who Led the Struggle, Publication (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Women and the Economy, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
    By Andrew Kohen; Susan Breinich; Patricia Shields. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Commission on the Status of Women A Progress Report, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Organize! A Working Women's Handbook, Publication (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Seventh Annual Report of the Director of the Women's Bureau, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Short Hours Pay, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: A Study of Employability of Women in Selected Sections of the United States, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Iva Lowther Peters. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Should There be Labor Laws for Women?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: The Distinct Problem of Women Employees, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Alfred Trembly. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Women in the Federal Service, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The Married Woman and her Job, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Edith Valet Cook. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Education for Marriage Series, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Janet Fowler Nelson. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Women Workers of Michigan, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: Women in Industry, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
    By Secretary of State. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Work Organization, Publication (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Toward Job Equality for Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By The conference Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Women Around the World, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Working-Class Women in a Changing World, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By Roger Coup; Shirley Greene; Burleigh Gardner. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Women in the Labor Movement, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: A Guide to Sources of Data on Women and Women Workers for the United States and for Regions, States, and Local Areas, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: From Sewing Machines to Politics: The Woman Union Member in the Community, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By Edna Raphael. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Changing Patterns of Women's Lives, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Sexual Harassment on the Workplace, Publication (Box 32, Folder 5)
    By Patricia Stover; Yvonne Gillies. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Women at Work: A Century of Industrial Change, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Recent Legislative and Executive Action Restricting the Right of Marriage Women to Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Women's Industrial Conference Number, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Women's Hours and Wages in the District of Columbia in 1937, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Women in Business, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Marketing Research Division. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Regional Conference of State Minimum-Wage Inspectors, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Summary of Conference Discussions. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Experience as to Standards for Women's Work in Periods of Rapid Increases in Production, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Effect of So-Called Married Women Bill on Business in General, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The Employer's Viewpoint on Regulatory Legislation for the Woman at Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Charles Craigmile. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Protection for Working Women, Publication (Box 32, Folder 6)
    By Alice Hamilton. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Conference on the Defence of Life, Publication (Box 32, Folder 7)
    By 4th Congress. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Workmen's Compensation 1910-1952: Are Present Benefits Adequate?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Harold Katz; Estelle Wirpel. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Development of Workmen's Compensation Claims Administration in the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Marshall Dawson. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Current Issues in Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Forces that Spiral Workmen's Compensation Costs, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Joseph Keiper. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: What's Wrong With Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By John P. Owen. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Rising Cost of Workmen's Compensation Cases and New Methods of Control, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Stanwood Hanson. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Workmen's Compensation, Fifty Years in Review, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By William Schnitzler. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Some Monetary Aspects of Wokmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By Council on Industrial Health. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Web and the Rock in Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 8)
    By James Reid. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Workmen's Compensation, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Selected References 1969-1971. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workmen's Compensation: A Bibliography, Publication (Box 32, Folder 9)
    By Margaret Chaplan. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Manpower Utilization in the Railroad Industry, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By Morris Horowitz. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Featherbedding, Work Rules, Restriction of Output, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Trends in Discipline and Work Rules, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: A Ray of Light in the Work Rules Dispute, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By H. E. Gilbert. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor and Industrial Relations Center, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By Charles Killingsworth. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Work Rules and Practices in Mass Production Industries, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: The Work-Rules Dispute, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Union Work Rules: A Brief Theoretical Analysis and Some Empirical Results, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
    By Paul Hartman. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Work Rules Issue in the Railroad Labor Dispute, Publication (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for the Desigh of New Careers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Sidney Fine. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Informal Factors in Career Achievement, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Melville Dalton. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Increasing Job Satisfaction of White-Collar Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Karlton Pierce; Thomas Beaver. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Study of Job Adjustment, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
    By Robert Carlson; Rene Dawis. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Promoting the Will to Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Job Satisfaction - A Review of Literature, Publication (Box 32, Folder 12)
    By Bonnie Carrol. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Job Satisfaction: A Review of the Literature, Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
    By Bonnie Carroll. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Humanist manifesto II, Publication (Box 32, Folder 13)
    By The Humanist. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Quality of Work Program: The First Eighteen Months, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Canadian Work Values: Findings of a Work Ethic Survey and a Job Satisfaction Survey, Publication (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Job Satisfaction a Bibliography from 1970, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    By Industrial relations Center. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Job Satisfaction Attitudes Surveys, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Towards the Measurement of Work Satisfaction, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    By Alan Portigal. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: A Work Experiment: Six Americans in a Swedish Plant, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Most Americans Like their Work, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: The Issues in the Debate: Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    By Al Nash. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: A Work Experiment, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    By Robert Goldman. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: A Descriptive Brochure, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: Information Update, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: A Path Analytic Study of the Structure of Employee Job Satisfactio: The Critical Role of Top Management, Publication (Box 32, Folder 15)
    By Richard Ruch. Item is in English.
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Concepts and Problems in Studies of the Quality of Working Life, Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
    By James Taylor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Progress in Improving the Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Book for Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    By John Connors. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Books for Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Annual Report, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    By American Federation of Labor. 1948-1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Books for Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    1937-1938. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Workers Education Bureau of America, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: A Reading List of the American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    By Frank Anderson; Davis Saposs. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Twenty-Fifth Anniversary Conference, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: The Party of Lenin and Stalin, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
    By George Count. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: AFL Sets up New Department of Education, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Item 10: Youth and the War on Poverty, Publication (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Box 32, Folder (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Biggest Obstacle to Youth Employment, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
    By Helen Harris. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Which Jobs for Young Workers?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Which Jobs for Young Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: Which Jobs for Young Workers, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: Which Jobs for Young Workers?, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Policies on Recruitment of Young Workers for Wartime Agriculture, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Urban Youth in the Labor Market, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
    By Works Projects Administration. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Challenge of Jobless Youth, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Trend Tables on Youth Employment and School Enrollment, Publication (Box 32, Folder 18)
    By Bureau of Labor Standards. 1940; 1944-1958. Item is in English.
- Box 33, Folder (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 27th Annual Conference, Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Alma Constitution, Publication (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Box 33, Folder (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement Between American Motors Corporation and the International Union Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and its Locals 72, 75, 206, 412, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between American Motors Corporation and the International Union Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and its Locals 72, 75, 206, 412, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between American Motors Corporation and the International Union Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and its Locals 72, 75, 206, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between American Motors Corporation and the International Union Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and its Locals 72, 75, Publication (Box 33, Folder 2)